Charles Perrone

6 Conant Valley Rd. perrone.c@husky.neu.edu
Pound Ridge, NY 10576 **Available: May – August 2013**914-420-9434

Objective

My interests are in securing summer employment to gain experience in the business environment, apply skills and understand the latest uses of information technology in business. I was chosen by Northeastern University as one of 400 accepted freshman to be part of a unique first semester spent studying in England. Through my commitment of over 10 years in scouting, I achieved the rank of Eagle Scout in 2011 and believe that experience has prepared me to take on challenges, help solve problems and work with teams.

EDUCATION September 2012 - Present

Northeastern University, Boston, MA

College of Computer and Information Science

Candidate for Bachelor of Science in Computer Science & Interactive Media

GPA: Pending

Related Courses: Fundamentals of Computer Science, Discrete Structures

John Jay High School, Cross River, NY June 2012

Honors: Honor Roll

Activities: Eagle Scout Vista Troop 101, Vocal Jazz, Jazz Band

Related Courses: Honors Algebra, Pre-Calculus, AP Macroeconomics, Environmental Physics

COMPUTER KNOWLEDGE

Languages: Scheme (Racket), HTML, CSS

Systems: Macintosh OS, Windows 98/XP/Vista

Software: Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Logic Pro 9, Photoshop, Illustrator

Other: GIT (Version Control System)

Work Experience

Plaza Theatrical Productions

Long Island, NY

Pit Musician October 2010 & August 2011

- Performed and practiced the scores for the musical productions of "13" and "Camp Rock"
- Aided in the organization and structure of rehearsals leading up to the performance

CT Ferrara Contracting South Salem, NY

General Laborer June 2011 - August 2011

- Provided preliminary demolition skills for a house renovation
- Assisted in painting, landscaping & yard maintenance on the property

Extracurricular Activites

- Musician compose and play guitar. Studied guitar under Micah Burgess & Scott Kacenga (NYU) and the legendary Arlen Roth for blues guitar 2009-2012.
- Eagle Scout learned leadership skills, teamwork, survival skills and attained Eagle rank after 10 year commitment to scouting. Only 2% of the nation's 800,000 boy scouts attain Eagle. My final project was to plan and lead the construction of a team building obstacle course at my high school.